NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{Infiltration
{Investigation?!
{A S-Class Mission Has Finally Arrived
It could be that way...
Sure enough, Ichiraku ramen is
the best for getting energized!
One more, Pops!
Coming right up!
Huh?
One more you said, eh...?
Just when I thought you'd snuck out of
your hospital room
and were doing some training...
You guys want some too?
Pops, here's the tab.
Thanks for your business!
Jeez, I'm fine!
Naruto-kun, even if it looks like you've healed
on the surface you're still battered.
It's not like that!
I have to train and get stronger!
Yeah, yeah,
after you've healed completely.
Damn it! I have to keep my promise
to Sakura without further delay...!
Sakura... You're so pathetic.
Naruto... This is a...
once in a lifetime request...
Please bring...
please bring Sasuke back.
I couldn't do it!
I wasn't able to stop Sasuke!
At this point, the only person who
would be able to stop Sasuke...
who would be able to save him...
Is you... Naruto...
All I did... was cry...
All I did was totally rely on Naruto.
I didn't do anything myself.
Naruto tried to bring back Sasuke-kun
even if it meant his life...
What can I do for Sasuke-kun now...?
I just have to put my life on the line
and do it!
It's futile. The ropes are made
of a maiden's black hair.
And the knot is a Shinobi
reverse butterfly knot.
It won't be easily untied.
Give me a break.
I have to start training as soon as possible
and get stronger.
Then do as the Medical Corps says
and rest quietly.
Come in.
Oh...
Sorry, Sakura-chan...
I'd like to get moving immediately
if possible but...
He has astonishing recuperative power
but overdoing it is a big no-no.
I'm okay!
Be a little more patient!
Just wait a little longer!
I'll keep my promise no matter what!
No...
It's okay...
Up until now
I was totally reliant on you...
and I did nothing so...
What's the matter, Sakura-chan...?
Did something happen?!
No... I'm was relieved
to see you doing well.
This time I'll do my best.
Sakura-chan...?
I heard you snuck out of the hospital.
Do you want to train that badly?
Pervy Sage...? My... apple!
Well well, things look
like they're going smoothly.
Don't you worry.
I'll train you hard right away.
Umm... about the training.
I was wondering if you could
wait a little while longer.
Hmm?
I'm not saying I don't want to train.
But I remembered some
odds and ends I need to take care of.
Oh?
Odds and ends, huh?
Come on. Please?
Come in!
Oh, I've been spotted, huh?
I'm guessing you want to peep?
No matter how long you wait
I won't show anything.
Wh-Who'd peep at an old lady?!
N-No I take that back!
Actually, I've come to make
an earnest request to you as the Hokage.
Talk.
This time I'll do my best.
It couldn't be that Sakura's going to...
This might be... my last look...
Sakura-chan...
How did you...?
I know what you're thinking!
That there'd be nothing
I could do even if I were to go...!
But I hate myself just standing here
doing nothing!
Always being a hindrance to
and taking advantage of everyone...
Not being able to do
one single thing respectably...
It's useless to stop me!
I won't stop you...
You should do it until you're satisfied.
But... I'm going too.
But...
It's become just the two of us...
But we're a three-man squad, right?
Yeah.
You guys...
Pervy Sage?
This person... is Jiraiya,
one of the legendary Sannin?
If you without permission,
go out past the border of
the Village Hidden in the Leaves...
you know at least that you'll be sent
to prison as Rogue Ninja, right?
It's no use stopping us!
I won't stop you.
You've been given a mission
by Hokage-sama.
You're to investigate and report
on the Land of Rice Paddies
where the Village Hidden in Sound is
and where Sasuke has been taken away.
The mission is set to be carried out
in a group of three.
As of now you will work under me.
You got a problem?!
It seems they're the biggest of fools.
They won't stop even if you tried.
At this rate
we'll lose two important subordinates!
You'll recognize it as a special mission
with the goal of investigating
the Village Hidden in Sound, right?
I have no choice, huh...?
But I have a condition.
Bring the two back alive. Got it?
Sure, even if it costs my life.
It's too dangerous of a mission even
with that Jiraiya going with them...
Sasuke-kun...
That's the Land of Rice Paddies where
the Village Hidden in the Sound is.
It's that Orochimaru's headquarters.
Take sufficient caution and proceed.
It's kind of anticlimactic...
Here I thought a bunch of
Orochimaru's followers would greet us!
Is this really the Hidden Sound Village?
It seems to be a peaceful
quiet and nice land but...
No, we still haven't entered
Village Hidden in the Sound.
This is the Land of Rice Paddies.
Land of Rice Paddies?
It's a small land that's nothing special.
The feudal lord was a foolish lord who
hungered for powerful military strength
in order to make the land
disproportionately larger.
And then Orochimaru probably won favor
with some fast-talking...
Of course Orochimaru himself wasn't
thinking about making the land stronger.
He just had an ambition to make himself
stronger and to carry out revenge...
That's why there's nothing in this area
that points to his presence.
Really? And so Pervy Sage...!
Don't call me Pervy Sage!
That's right...
He's one of the legendary Sannin so...
He's just a lady-loving
perverted Pervy Sage!
What?!
More importantly
where's the Village Hidden in the Sound?
Beats me... I don't know...
What?!
We don't know where it is
so we're going to investigate, right?
You've got a point but...
But how do we find it?
There can't be a place where
people are without food and ladies.
People gather where
there's food and girls!
— Where people gather there's news.
— There goes Pervy Sage's bad habit.
He's planning to sow his wild oats
under the guise of a special mission.
First off, finding a traveler's town with
lots of hot ladies is the top priority!
Every land should have a traveler's town.
"Lodging"
This is a traveler's town... right?
Looks like nobody's living here anymore.
No, I feel the presence of people...
And the smell of face powder!
— Naruto, take it out.
— Take what out?
Don't act as you don't know!
In anything one does
a war chest is necessary, right?
What! Are you after my wallet? Man!
What?! This shouldn't be it!
Try jumping!
Huh?!
No! Stop!
One, two, three... Is this all you got?
That's all of it really!
— Here...
— Huh?
It's not much but please use it.
No! Sakura-chan there's no need for
you to give that to him!
But it's money for
gathering information, right?
Right, right. This should be enough.
You guys go on ahead to the outskirts
of the post station and wait!
Wh-Why?
It's too dangerous ahead from here.
It's a mission for adults.
Hmm, the smell of
face powder's from here.
Welcome...
Along came a sucker just begging
to be parted from his money.
We should be able to pulverize him.
Food and Drink! And young women!
Even if you give the Pervy Sage money
he's just going to sow his oats without
gathering any information anyway.
Sow his oats...?
Y-Yeah...
I don't really know about it but...
You know make-out blah-blah-blah...
It's fine!
If I can be of at least some help...
I'm always a hindrance
who can't do anything so...
It's not like that!
In the first place
if you hadn't taken the action...
I'd still be tied to the bed!
"Brothel"
Even in different lands
there are young women everywhere.
So? Why don't we move to
the room in the back?
I want to talk more relaxed.
Nice, nice.
Then first settle up the tab
for here, okay?
What am I already drunk
on this cheap drink...?
Aren't there like three too many zeros?
You like to joke, do you?
If you value your life
leave all you've got on you here.
I see how it is.
Master Jiraiya's late.
I'm sick of waiting.
Naruto!
Who's there?!
Who're you?!
Are you one of Orochimaru's followers?!
What? Was I wrong?!
Damn it.
That kid had erased his presence
until he'd gotten that close.
I won't let him get away!
Don't move!
Wh-Why?!
Makibishi Spikes!
Naruto!
Wh-What?!
— Hold it! You jerk!
— We won't let you get away!
Naruto, what's that?!
Pervy Sage? What did you do?!
I'll tell you later!
Anyway, let's get out of here!
Why?!
Companions of the person just now?
If they're Orochimaru's followers
with my Shadow Clone Jutsu I'll...
No no! Don't get the wrong idea!
They're just bodyguards from a rip-off bar!
R-Rip-off bar...?!
First and foremost this mission has
to be carried out in strict secrecy!
There'd be no point if you were
to use Ninja Art and stand out!
You! Carry the bags!
The one who's totally standing out
is you Pervy Sage!
You have a point.
This is wrong!
Will we really reach Sasuke like this?!
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
Jeez, this is an appallingly unsettled town.
Well, you guys wait here.
Huh? Why?!
Infiltrating up ahead is too dangerous!
It's too much for you youngsters.
Pervy Sage...
I myself should be the only sacrifice!
See ya, Naruto.
Blah-blah-blah trying to look good...
Your scheme to go into
a weird shop again is totally obvious!
Next time:
"The Town of Outlaws. The Shadow of the Fuma Clan."